ENRIQUE REYES JENSEN

Madrid, Spain | M: +34 655 148 250 | ereyesj8@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/1enriquereyesj

PROFESIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable and result oriented MSc business analytics student with strong business management and finance background. Quick learner and hardworking individual with assorted strategy consultancy experience. Passionate for technological and strategical solutions that drive and transform businesses to success.

EDUCATION

IE Business School Madrid, Spain

MSc in Big Data & Business Analytics

October 2021 – July 2022

Relevant Coursework:

Machine Learning, Python for Data Analysis, AI, SQL, Big Data in Business Strategy, Data Visualization

IE University Madrid, Spain

Bachelor of Business Administration

September 2015 – June 2019

Relevant Coursework:

• Corporate Finance, Cross Border M&A, Valuation of Privately Held Companies, International Finance, Advance Analysis of Financial Statements, Advance Excel for Decision Making, Lean Management

EXPERIENCE

Laborde Consultores, Management Consulting

Madrid, Spain

Operations & Strategy Consultant

October 2019 – October 2021

- Developed proposals and presentations for potential clients providing efficient ad-hoc solutions
- Lead projects alongside third-party consultants to provide import licenses and market studies for companies such as Telcomdis, Royal Progress and QD Health
- Participate in various performance improvements consulting projects with important companies amongst Telecommunications, Financial & Credit Cards and Online Betting industries.

Innobooster, Private Innovation Agency

Madrid, Spain

Summer Intern & Junior Consultant

June -September 2018 & June - October 2019

- Analysed business plans for startups and assessed their potential to obtain funding
- Conducted detailed regional market research to understand the fundamentals of business models and identify strengths and weakness for financing possibilities
- Organized workshops with INDRA and ENDESA to promote financing opportunities for startups
- Participated in processes that in aggregate raised USD +3 million from the "Centro para el Desarrollo Tecnológico e Industrial" for different Spanish startups

Banco de Occidente, Grupo Aval Bank

Cali, Colombia

Risk Management Summer Intern

June 2017 – August 2017

- Analysed valuations of financial derivatives as a risk management indicator on the bank's subsidiaries in Panama and Barbados
- Backed the Compliance Officer in submission of regulatory information for the treasury management division

Smurfit Kappa Group, Manufacturing & Packaging

Cali, Colombia

Paper Mill Division Summer Intern

June 2016 – August 2016

• Pursued an intensive search to locate a third-party storage management company which helped resolve inventory related issues and assisted in the outsourcing of a warehouse during a local transportation strike

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills: Microsoft Office Tools Advance User, SQL, Python, PowerBI, Gretl, Pipedrive, Dataiku, NoSQL, Spark **Notas de Paz Foundation:** Teaching kids to read and encouraging them in their dream of becoming musicians

Hobbies: IE University Varsity Federated Football Team, Padel, Polo, Tennis, Robotics, Trumpet

Languages: Fluent in both English and Spanish

Work Permit: EU Work Permit holder